Miyama
Here.
You said you wanted to
look at this, didn't you?
She's cute...
I wouldn't mind letting her...
mess up my life.
Best Kushikatsu in Japan
Yokozuna
Pub
Ain't no place
for losers here
Hey, Gramps!
The hell is this?
Oh?
A Huge Shakeup in the Yakuza World?
The Kingpins of Kanto and Kansai
Finally Call a Truce?!
The Biggest in Kansai! The Fourth-Generation
Kirigaya-gumi Direct Subsidiary Somei-gumi
Leader Somei Renji
and
The Biggest in Kanto! Fifth-Generation
Tokusa-gumi Direct Subsidiary Miyama
Family Leader Miyama Gaku Swore an Oath
of Brotherhood!!
"A Huge Shakeup in the Yakuza World"?
Hey, I look really handsome here.
Kirigaya-gumi Direct Subsidiary
Somei-gumi Leader
Somei Renji
Kiri
You moron!
No one gives a crap about that!
I'm talkin' about the last part!
"Apparently, their grandchildren
are rather close,
and according to sources
close to the families,
they may be getting engaged
in the near future."
This better not be talkin' about me!
Who else would it be?
God damn it!
First off, I've never met this Miyama
or whoever from Tokyo or their grandson!
Who the hell're these "sources"?!
Me, of course!
Huh?
Yoshino, you're turning 17
this year, aren't ya?
But you haven't even been with a boy yet.
And since you're so lonely...
I found you a guy myself!
Booooooooooom
I mean, Miyama's grandson is quite the looker!
The Biggest in Kanto!
Fifth-Generation Tokusa-gumi
Direct Subsidiary Miyama
Family Leader Miyama Gaku
He looks just like Gaku when he was young!
Honestly, I was shocked.
Gramps, you've known this
Miyama guy for a while now?
If I didn't, I wouldn't have suggested you.
Just so you know, I ain't gettin' married!
Oh, quit your yappin' and
at least meet the guy first!
Or your life's gonna end with you never
talkin' to a young guy that ain't family!
M-Mind your own damn business
and leave me alone!
Not to mention you were
blessed with my genetics
and turned out hot, yet you
never let your damn guard down.
You keep sayin' that I'm hot,
but it's because of this face people
keep saying I'm an Umeda hostess
or that I'm divorced with a child!
Meh, who cares?
Why don't you try livin' in Tokyo?
You can transfer there.
You're basically bilingual since you can
speak Tokyo Japanese and Kansai Japanese!
They're both Japanese!
I don't even know this guy's
name or what he looks like!
Well, his name is Miyama Kirishima!
What? Is that like his yakuza name?
You moron. That's his real
name. He ain't no yakuza.
I'm tellin' you, he's in high school.
Anyway, just go to Tokyo
and see for yourself.
Then we can talk.
In the end, I actually came.
It's huge.
Tokusa-gumi Direct Subsidiary
Miyama Family Leader
Miyama Gaku
Tokusa
Thanks for traveling so far.
H-He's so handsome!
You actually do look like Renji.
Anyone ever tell you that?
All the time, actually.
That I look like Renji when he was
young but if he was a girl.
Damn straight.
U-Um, by the way, so where is
this Miyama Kirishima-san...?
Huh? What're you talking about?
He's standing right behind you.
That worked better than I thought it would.
Hello, it's nice to meet
you. I'm Miyama Kirishima.
Huh? Uh...
Whoops, sorry. Did I scare you?
I just couldn't find the right moment.
R-Right...
I'll go ahead and show you
around the rest of the place.
H-Hey, wait!
What do you think?
About what?
We heard you were going to
be living with us in Tokyo,
so we had the tea room
of this annex remodeled.
Huh?!
It's separated from the main house, so we
thought you'd feel a little more relaxed.
Sorry, can I say something?
I really appreciate you guys
doing all of this for me...
but I haven't decided on if
I'm actually coming here.
If I end up declining this offer...
Oh, sorry. I forgot to mention that.
Sorry for jumping the gun.
Huh?
Of course, we don't mind if
you decline this offer at all.
I mean, you were pretty much forced into it.
I mean, a guy and a girl who'd never met
before preparing to marry each other?
Talk about old-fashioned.
T-True...
I honestly thought you
wouldn't even come up here.
Huh?
I was really happy when they
told me you'd at least come to meet me.
That's genuinely enough. Thanks.
Oren Private High School
I was just saying he didn't seem so bad,
and somehow I ended up transferring here.
I mean, if we're being honest, I'm
the pushover in this situation...
I can't help but feel like I got duped!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Yoshino.
It took a while to figure out our classes.
Is something wrong?
N-No, I'm fine.
You have fine arts classes, don't you?
Yeah. And you're concentrating
on math and science, aren't you?
That's amazing.
I'm not smart,
so I was worried if I could even
transfer into such a high-level school.
So, Kirishima-kun...
"Kirishima-kun" is a bit embarrassing.
If you don't mind, could
you just call me Kirishima?
Huh? Uh, er, then, um...
Do you always get rides to
and from school, Kirishima?
No way. I got a ride today, but
usually, I just take the train.
Should we get you a ride to
and from school, Yoshino?
Huh? No, I'm fine...
I see.
Your class is back there, Yoshino.
Well, see you after school.
It's hard to imagine he was
born in a yakuza family...
Thank goodness he's just
a normal, nice person.
Hey, do you have a second?
Huh? M-Me?
Yeah.
Sorry. No one's ever really
talked to me at school before.
Huh?
S-So, how can I help you?
You came to school this morning
with Miyama-kun, didn't you?
Huh? Um...
I heard you came from Osaka. Are you
Miyama-kun's relative or something?
Huh? No, I'm not his relative...
Our families are close...
You're not his girlfriend, are you?
G-Girlfriend?!
No, er, I'm not his girlfriend...
but we may end up living together...
Hang on a second!
Stop beating around the bush and answer us.
That's enough. Let's go.
Huh? What?
Man, I'm really being
gawked at by the girls...
Yoshino.
Did you see that?
Miyama-kun's so hot!
What's wrong, Yoshino?
Er, I guess you're really... popular.
You think so?
No one talks to me other than to greet me,
and everyone knows I'm
the grandson of a yakuza.
Oh, really? I thought they didn't know...
Aren't they scared?
In this day in age, if you report
that a yakuza did something to you,
the police would come running.
Even if someone's a yakuza, they're
not scary if they can't do anything.
I see...
You don't hate it, Kirishima?
Huh?
Like... doesn't it get annoying
to have people look at you weird?
Annoying?
Nah, I can't say I ever thought
about that. I don't really care.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Oh, damn it! I can't sleep!
Ugh, tomorrow's gonna suck if I can't sleep!
I don't really care.
He seemed like someone completely different.
I'll drink some water.
Blood?
He looks like a yakuza.
Sorry. I figured I could buy daily
necessities when I came over here.
I hate to ask, but would you come with me?
Sure. Is tonight okay?
Y-Yeah.
All right. See you then.
That was standoffish.
Maybe I was imagining it.
No, but I mean...
I wonder what he was doing.
No, no. What am I even talking about?
Am I that exhausted from not enough sleep?
I finally saw that transfer student.
She's so flashy.
I'm gonna be shocked if he that's his type.
You know what Miyama-kun's
house is like, don't you?
Well, I heard she was working as a
prostitute so she could pay off some debt to them.
No way!
Actually, I can see that.
Just look at her face.
God, this is such a pain!
I guess this is the same in Tokyo or Osaka.
What a pain in the ass.
S-Sorry, one sec!
Do you mind if I withdraw
some cash at the store?
I'll be right back!
Wait right here!
Hey, miss! Your skirt's flipped.
Huh?! What?!
Huh?
Oh, my bad. I guess I was seein' things.
Sorry.
You goin' out somewhere?
You reek of alcohol.
You heading to work now?
You work around here?
Huh? No, I'm not like that...
Want us to take you?
W-Wait, are they...
Hitting on me
I've never had any guys talk
to me in town other than
Old Man Imai from the shopping district!
You're as pretty as ever.
Really?
Hey, don't worry. We'll make
sure you get where you need to.
Huh? No, wait! I have someone waiting for me.
What?!
Just shut your mouth and come with us!
N-No, really...
Don't try to fight back.
It's a pain in the ass.
Who the hell are you?
Yeah, so that girl's with me.
Let's go.
Get lost before you get hurt!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Huh!?
Huh?
Y-You bastard!
K-Kirishima! I think that's enough...
Oh, sorry. It'll just be a little longer.
Hey, are you listening?
Hey, remember my face.
That girl's mine,
so make sure you never talk to her again.
Also, tell the rest of your friends
about me the best you can.
You can try to get revenge,
but if you do, just know I'll
kill you and anyone close to you.
Got it?
Yes...
Okay, let's go, Yoshino.
Huh? Shouldn't we call an ambulance?
Nah, they won't die or anything.
You've never had guys like that
hit on you before, have you?
Huh?
That's because the people around you knew
that you were Boss Somei's granddaughter.
And I'm sure you always had someone with you.
Some guy that definitely didn't
look like some upstanding citizen.
You should be more careful.
This isn't Osaka, after all.
Sorry, I...
It's fine. Let's go.
Wait a sec. At this rate, someone
might call the police...
Oh, it's fine.
Where's my handkerchief...
Hey, that's...
Huh?
Oh, didn't I tell you?
Sorry to scare you. I'll
be more careful next time.
Next time?
Something wrong?
Uh, s-sorry! I-I...
Yeah, I can't anymore.
This is a pain in the ass.
Huh??
I honestly had high hopes for you, Yoshino.
You're not only the granddaughter of
the leader of the Somei-gumi that's
affiliated with the Kirigaya-gumi,
but you're also hot.
I figured you were spoiled
rotten, insanely selfish,
and probably some chick who thought
the world revolved around her.
I love girls who are hated by other girls.
I absolutely love having some girl
who doesn't have a single girlfriend
lead me on with absolutely
no mercy or humanity.
What are you...
You don't understand what I'm saying?
Basically, you're way more normal than I
could've imagined, so I got bored with you.
I thought you'd at least keep
me entertained for a year,
but you're already a pain to deal with now.
Though this is my own fault for
having such high hopes for you.
What do you want to do? Go back to Osaka?
You can stay here if you want,
but right now, you're just some chick
with absolutely no value to me.
If you're gonna stay, could you
at least be of some use to me?
What?
You're only good for your
face and your body, right?
Why not sell your body and make some cash?
We actually work with an escort service.
If you work really hard,
you should easily be able to make
a million in like two months.
They pride themselves on
quality and hygiene, too.
Oh, you've got milder options
like facials and vibrators, too.
If you don't think you can
handle that, you can go home.
If you go back to Osaka, tell them
exactly what I just said to you.
It'd be awesome if this ends
up starting some shit again.
My life might actually be over. I can't wait.
I never imagined that a guy like
that existed in this world.
Maybe I will go back to Osaka.
It hasn't even been that long yet though.
Huh? Mud?
The hell's mud doing in here?
Wait... could this be...
Bullying
Bullying?
Modern
You can't be serious.
I've never seen such a stereotypical
example of this in my life.
I guess I'll take a picture.
Come on, that's going too far!
You're the one who said we should do it!
Shoma
What are you doing in Tokyo?
Seriously, what am I doing?
I wanna go back to Osaka.
No, wait. What am I saying?
Somei Renji
Hey, Yoshino! It's your Gramps!
You doin' good?
Yeah, but... What? Is something wrong?
Nah, we were all just talkin' about
the fact that you might be homesick.
What? What's wrong?
No, it's just...
Are you cryin'?
You couldn't even beat around the bush?
Thing's goin' good with
you and Miyama's grandson?
One year.
No matter how much they oppress you,
no matter how much they ostracize you,
no matter how much things don't go
right, don't come back here for a year.
Latch on like your life depends on it.
You got that, Yoshino?
Spend the next year makin'
that grandson of Miyama's
fall so madly in love with you it kills him.
And then after a year, dump
his ass and come back home.
That's the best revenge you can get on a guy.
I'm sayin' that plenty of
women dumped my ass, too!
When I was younger, I
got caught three-timing,
and when those three threw me into
a lake, I thought I was a goner!
Talk to ya later, Yoshino.
I'll call you again. Bye!
All the men in my life are nothing but trash.
Well, I guess I'm gonna have to
live up to your expectations.
Hello? It's Yoshino...
I haven't seen that chick around lately.
Yeah... She just upped and
disappeared about two weeks ago.
Hey, you didn't do anything, did you?
The boss is gonna kill you.
And the thrill of that danger
is what makes me do it.
You're so creepy, you damn masochist.
Mornin'.
It's been a while. You been good?
Of course.
How about you, Yoshino?
I've been doin' all right.
Did you think I went back to Osaka?
To be honest, yeah.
Remember when you said that I was
only good for my face and my body?
And that I should sell
my body for some money.
Yeah, I do.
Honestly, that creeped me out.
And well, I did sell my body.
I sold one of my kidneys for 4 mil.
Your kidney? Where?
Shikoku: A contact of a contact of a contact.
I had them take it with an endoscope.
I'm gonna have to live the rest of
my life watchin' my salt intake.
Anyway, I'm gonna go back to my class.
Also, I ain't goin' back to Osaka.
I could give a rat's ass if you're
some masochistic piece of shit.
But you know what'll happen if you
get too ahead of yourself, right?
Hey!
I'm talkin' to you three, too.
No matter how much I try to make an honest
livin', I'm gonna die a real shitty death.
In that case...
Even if I have to crawl around
on the floor and cough up blood,
I'll take y'all down to hell
with me and ruin your lives!
Anyway, just thought you should know.
Uh? What?
I love you!
I've never felt so excited in my life!
I'm still excited!
That must mean that I
love you, right, Yoshino?
Wait, what?
I love you! Let's absolutely get married!
I want you to mess up my life!
What?!
You've got to be messed up in the head!
Did you already forget what
you told me the other day?!
Yeah, I'm really sorry about that!
But I know now! I was wrong!
No, really! I'm in love with you!
I've got a boner right now!
Oren Private High School
You're so gross!
All right, I see.
I'll tell my boys, too.
Talk to ya later.
Is something the matter?
Something really annoying just happened...